offermatic.com 2012-01-13

# Offermatic--Offers That Matter, Directly To You Card

**Date Last Revised: July 12, 2011**  
Offermatic is committed to maintaining the security of any personal information about our members. This Privacy and Security Policy explains how we protect personal information provided through our website [www.offermatic.com](http://www.offermatic.com/) (the “Site”) and how we use that information in connection with our service offered through the Site (the “Service”). “Personal information” for purposes of this Policy means information that identifies you, such as your name, address or email address. Offermatic stresses its privacy and security standards to guard against identity theft and provide security for your personal information. We regularly re-evaluate our privacy and security policies and adapt them as necessary to deal with new challenges. 

## TRUSTe

Offermatic is certified through the TRUSTe Web Privacy Seal Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. In order to obtain certification, Offermatic disclosed its information privacy practices to TRUSTe for its review to ensure compliance with TRUSTe�s requirements. If you contact us with a privacy-related concern as directed in this Policy and do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or if your inquiry is not satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php>. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

## Your Privacy is not for sale

We do not and will not sell your personal information to anyone. Offermatic uses and discloses your personal information only as follows: 

  * to analyze site usage and improve the Service;
  * to deliver to you any administrative notices and communications relevant to your use of the Service;
  * to fulfill your requests for certain products and services;
  * for market research, project planning, troubleshooting problems, detecting and protecting against error, fraud or other criminal activity;
  * to third-party contractors that provide services to Offermatic and are bound by these same privacy restrictions;
  * to enforce Offermatic’s Terms of Use; and
  * as otherwise set forth in this Privacy and Security Policy.

## We limit the collection and use of personal information

Certain areas and features of Offermatic.com are available to you without registration or the need to provide to us any information. However, other features of the Site or the Service may require registration, which involves provision to Offermatic of an email address, a password and your zip code and to participate on our forum boards, a username (collectively the “Registration Information”). In order to benefit from the full functionality of the Service, you also must provide your third-party account credentials (“Account Credentials”) to allow Offermatic to access your account information at those other financial institutions (“Account Information”) for your use.

From time to time we may request other personal information to provide you with other benefits of the Service. In all such instances, you will be given the opportunity to provide or to decline to provide that information, and it will be used only for the stated purpose. Offermatic may make anonymous or aggregate personal information and disclose such information only in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes.

Such information does not identify you individually. Access to your Registration Information, Account Credentials, Account Information and any other personal information you provide is strictly restricted and used in accordance with specific internal procedures and safeguard governing access, in order to operate, develop or improve the Service. These individuals have been selected in accordance with our security policies and practices and are bound by confidentiality obligations. They may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

## Online session information and use is only used to improve your experience

When you visit Offermatic.com, we may collect technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, Internet protocol address, pages visited, and average time spent on our Site. This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve our Web design and functionality.

“Cookies” are alphanumeric identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored by your Web browser on your computer’s hard drive. Offermatic may set and access cookies on your computer to track and store preferential information about you. Offermatic may gather information about you through cookie technology. Please note that most Internet browsers will allow you to stop cookies from being stored on your computer and to delete cookies stored on your computer. If you choose to eliminate cookies, the full functionality of the Service may be impaired for you. We encode our cookies so that only we can interpret the information stored in them.

Web beacons are images embedded in a Web page or email for the purpose of measuring and analyzing site usage and activity. Offermatic, or third party service providers acting on our behalf, may use Web beacons to help us analyze Site usage and improve the Service.

We may use third party service providers to help us analyze certain online activities. For example, these service providers may help us measure the performance of our online campaigns or analyze visitor activity on Offermatic.com. We may permit these service providers to use cookies and other technologies to perform these services for Offermatic. We do not share any personal information about our customers with these third party service providers, and these service providers do not collect such information on our behalf. Our third party service providers are required to comply fully with this Privacy and Security Policy.

## Third parties offering other products or services will not be given your personal information without your permission

There are a number of separate products and services offered by third parties advertised by us on our Site and through the Service. If you choose to use these separate products or services, disclose information to the providers, or grant them permission to collect information about you, then their use of your information is governed by their privacy policies. You should evaluate the practices of external services providers before deciding to use their services. Offermatic is not responsible for their privacy practices. If you click on a link to a third party site, Offermatic encourages you to check the privacy policy of that site. Offermatic may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed and whether any action has been taken on a third party Web site. 

## Blogs and other Forums on Offermatic.com

If you use a bulletin board, blog or chat room on our Site, you should be aware that any information you submit there can be read, collected or used by other members and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these forums. These forums may be hosted by Offermatic or by one of our third party service providers on Offermatic's behalf. 

## Disclosure of your information to protect our rights or if required by law

Notwithstanding the foregoing, Offermatic reserves the right (and you authorize Offermatic) to share or disclose your personal information when Offermatic determines, in its sole discretion, that the disclosure of such information is necessary or appropriate: 

  * To enforce our rights against you or in connection with a breach by you of this Privacy and Security Policy or the Offermatic.com Terms of Use;
  * To prevent prohibited or illegal activities; or
  * When required by any applicable law, rule regulation, subpoena or other legal process.

## Your information may be transferred upon change of control but only in accordance with this Policy

Personal information may be transferred to a third party as a result of a sale, acquisition, merger, reorganization or other change of control. If we sell, merge or transfer any part of our business, part of the sale may include your personal information. If so, you will be asked if you’d like to stop receiving promotional information following any change of control. 

## Email communications from us

We allow members to subscribe to email newsletters and from time to time may transmit emails promoting Offermatic or third-party goods or services. Offermatic.com subscribers have the ability to opt-out of receiving our promotional emails and to terminate their newsletter subscriptions by following the instructions in the emails. 

## Your information is secure

We use a combination of firewall barriers, encryption techniques and authentication procedures, among others, to maintain the security of your online session and to protect Offermatic.com accounts and systems from unauthorized access. When you register for the Service, Offermatic requires a password from you for your privacy and security. Offermatic transmits information such as your Registration Information for Offermatic.com or Account Credentials securely.

Offermatic has been verified by Verisign for its use of SSL encryption technologies and audited by TRUSTe for its privacy practices. In addition, Offermatic tests the Site daily for any failure points that would allow hacking.However, it is important to understand that these precautions apply only to our Site and systems. We exercise no control over how your information is stored, maintained or displayed by third parties or on third-party sites.

## Our service ensures secure communications with encryption

From the time you submit your Login ID and Password, these communications between your computer and Offermatic.com are encrypted. This enables client and server applications to communicate in a way that is designed to prevent eavesdropping, tampering and message forgery. 

## We post updates on our website whenever there is a change to our Privacy and Security Policy

We update this Privacy and Security Policy periodically. The date last revised appears at the top of the Policy. Changes take effect immediately upon posting. 

## Contact us if you have any questions or concerns

If you have questions, comments, concerns or feedback regarding this Privacy and Security Policy or any other privacy or security concern, contact us. 

Offermatic Inc.   
111 E. 5th Avenue, San Mateo, CA 94401
